It's Samar's birthday. Samar loves maths. He likes to cut his cake such a way that all the pieces of cake cut by him is a power of 2.

Given the size of the cake, find out the minimum number of pieces of cake Samar can cut.

Input:
- The First line will contain an integer $n$, specifying the number of test cases. $n$ test cases follow.
- Each line of the test case contains an integer $p$ which specifies the size of the cake.

Output:
For each test case, output is the minimum number of pieces Samar can get by cutting the cake into pieces, size of which is a power of 2.

Contraints:
1 ≤ n ≤ 10^2

Subtasks:
- 30 points: 1 ≤ p ≤ 10^2
- 70 points: 1 ≤ p ≤ 10^3

Sample Input:
3
7
8
27

Sample Output:
3
1
4

Explanation:
Test Case #1: When the size of the cake is 7, it can be divided into 3 pieces of sizes 4,2,1. Hence, the output is 3

Test Case #2: When the size of the cake is 8, Samar will not cut it into pieces because 8 itself is a power of 2 (2^3). So, the whole 8 size piece is a single piece. Hence, the output is 1

Test Case #3: When the size of the cake is 15, it can be divided into 4 pieces of sizes 16,8,2,1.