After Pulwama Attack, Indian Army decided a second Surgical Strike to kill all the terrorists involved in the attack.

But this time, Pakistan is well prepared.

On the way to terrorist camps, Indian Army encountered a Minefield. If the soldier steps on a mine, it will trigger all other mines and the whole squad will die. Minesweeper of the team found out where the mines are placed. He found that the terrorists have placed the mines in such a ways that there is exactly one direct path from their starting location to the terrorist camps.

He divided the land into modules of a grid with horizontal distance as $x$ and vertical distance as $y$ (in simple words: matrix form). He assigned each module with an integer value from 1 to $x*y$. For each module which has mine, he marked $1$ if the module of the grid contains mine and $0$ if it doesn't contain mine. Soldiers can only walk on the path where there are no mines.

Their starting position is always considered as $(1,1)$ and destination (terrorist camp) as $(x,y)$. Also, they can only move in either horizontal or vertical direction at a time (no diagonals).

Find out the path they should choose in order to accomplish their mission successfully.

###Input:

- The First line contains two integers $x$ and $y$ which defines the size of the matrix (grid).
- First line is followed by $x*y$ integers which are the elements of the matrix. The value of the element is $1$ if mine is present and $0$ if it is not present.

###Output:
Set of integers (separated by spaces) from 1 to x*y which specifies the path Indian Army should choose in order to reach their destination.

###Subtasks
- 30 points:
	- 1 ≤ x ≤ 10
	- 1 ≤ y ≤ 10

- 70 points: 
	- 1 ≤ x ≤ 10^3
	- 1 ≤ y ≤ 10^3

###Sample Input:
5 5
0 0 0 1 1
1 1 0 1 1
1 0 0 1 1
1 0 1 1 1
1 0 0 0 0

###Sample Output:
1 2 3 8 13 12 17 22 23 24 25 
	
###EXPLANATION:
Here the grid size is (5,5), so there are 5x5=25 modules in it. The 0's defines the path squad should choose (Note: first position (top left) and the destination (bottom right) is always 0)

The values are assigned to the elements of the matrix in the following way:

	$1$  2  3  4  5
	$6$  $7$  8  9  10
	11 $12$ 13 14 15
	16 $17$ $18$ $19$ $20$
	21 22 23 24 $25$

To go from position 1 to position 25, the only path is though 6,7,12,17,18,19 and 20 (1 to 7 is not allowed because squad cannot move diagonally).